Emmanuel TV Partners Receiving The New Morning Water In South Africa
Attention all Emmanuel TV viewers!
Are you an Emmanuel TV viewer living in Europe, Asia, North or South America, Australia or Africa?
Are you called to join us in changing lives, nations, and the world by becoming an Emmanuel TV partner?
Join us for a special meeting with the Emmanuel TV team sent by Prophet T.B. Joshua
with the New Morning Water at the following locations:
Birmingham, UK - Saturday the 27th of January 2018;
Paris, France - watch out for more information coming soon.
For UK, contact: +44 798 503 4222,
e-mail: uk@emmanuel.tv
For France, contact: +33 142 888 047,
e-mail: fr@emmanuel.tv
"The beauty of life does not depend on how happy you are
but on how happy others can be because of you."
- T.B. Joshua